Conrail Merger Documents 6093
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Conrail Merger Documents
1997-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Conrail (Consolidated Rail Corporation)
6093
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Records.
5794415
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroads --United States-- Finance; Railroads -- Mergers -- United States; ConRail; Consolidated Rail Corporation; ConRail -- Archives
5794415
- Documents and Transcripts. (Box 1)
  - National Mining Assn. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NEFCO (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - N.E. Illinois Regional Commuter RR Corp. Regional Transportation Authority (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NJ Transp. Planning Auth. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Comments and Requests for Request for Conditions of New Jersey Department of Transportation and New Jersey Transit Corporation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Comments and Request for Conditions of Northern Virginia Transportation Commission and Potomac and Rappahannock Transportation Commission (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Assn. RR Passengers (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Lime and Stone Co. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Conrail Merger w/ CSX (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - JFC BLE NYSLB (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Transcripts. (Box 2)
  - NJ Transit Corporation (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Norfolk Southern (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    -operating plan, shared assets, joint verified statements:Spenski & Peifer, Labor Impact Exhibit
  - Norfolk-Southern STB F.D#33388 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Northern Indiana Public Service Company (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NYS-DOT (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NYSEG (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ohio Rail Development (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Valley Coal Co. Ohio Mining (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Orange + Rockland Utilities (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - PA House Transp. Comm. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - PA Power & Light (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Philadelphia Belt Line RR (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Port Authority of NY&NJ (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Potomac Electric Power co. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - PPG Industries (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Rail-Bridge Terminals (NJ) Corporation (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Regional Railroads of America (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rhode Island DOT (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rocky River Ohio (City of) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Shell Chemical (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Society of the Plastics (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - S.E. PA Transp. Authority (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Stark Development (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - State of Illinois (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - TMA/COG (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Transportation Intermediaries Assn. (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Transcripts. (Box 3)
  - Transtar, Inc., Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Rwy. Co. and Wisconsin Central, Ltd., Lake Erie RR. Co. - Emergency Appeal (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Union Pacific RR Co. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Dept. of Justice (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - US DOT (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - UTU-NASCA (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vermont Railway (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Village of Ridgeview Park, NJ (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Weirton Steel Corporation (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Rwy Co. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wisconsin Central Fox Valley and Western Ltd. Sault Ste. Marie Bridge Co. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Withdrawals of Parties (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Erie-Niagara Rail Steering Joseph Smith and Sons Inc. Institute of Scrap Recycling Cargill, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Allied Rail Unions - Response to Environmental Report (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Transcripts and AK Steel Box. (Box 4)
  - American Electric Power, Atlantic City Electric Co., Delmarva Power and Light Co. Indianapolis Power and Light Company (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - American Short Line RR Assn. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - American Trucking Assns., Inc. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Amtrak (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Amvest Corporation Vaughan RR Co. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Anker Energy, et al. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ann Arbor RR (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ashta Chemicals, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - A.T. Massey Coal Co. and Affiliates (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bay State Milling Co. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Belvidere & Delaware River Railway Black River & Western RR (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo & Pittsburgh Railroad and Allegheny & Eastern RR (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Burlington-Northern (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Canadian National & Grand Trunk Western (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Canadian Pacific D&H, Soo Line & St. Lawrence & Hudson Railways: Verified Statement (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Central RR Co. of Indiana (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Champion International Corp. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Chemical Manufact - Urer's Association (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Citizens Advisory (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chicago Metra (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Citizens Gas & Coke Utility (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - City of Cincinnati (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - AK Steel (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Transcripts and Documents. (Box 5)
  - City of Cleveland (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - City of Indianapolis (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - City of Lakewood Ohio (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Conrail (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Conrail Retirees (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Central RR Co. of Indiana (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Coneg - Coalition of Northeastern Governors (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Consumers Energy co. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Delaware DOT (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Detroit-Edison (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Eastern Shore RR, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Eastman Kodak (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - FINA (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - FourCity (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gateway Western (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - General Mills (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - GPU Generation, Inc. The Four City Consortium Detroit Edison Co. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Gra, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Housatonic RR (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Illinois Central RR Co.Central and Pacific Co. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - City of Indianapolis (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Iowa Interstate RR Inc. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Kansas City Southern Rwy Co. Gateway Western Rwy. Co. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Kokomo Grain Co. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - OH- 10th District Congressman Dennis J. Kucinich (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - A. Herb Kerekesch George Donahue (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Livonia, Avon & Lakeville Railroad Companies (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Louisville & Indiana RR Co. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Maine DOT (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Martin Marietta Materials, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Maryland DOT (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Massachusetts Central RR Corp. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Metro-North (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - AFF & Exhibits Of (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Exhibits and Files. (Box 6)
  - STB Protective Order (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - STB Decision 21 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - STB Decision #21 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - STB Decision 43 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rpt. To Erie - Niagara Steering Committee (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Impact Summ. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Economic Impact (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Tom Roberts (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - UTU (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Rail Mergers (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - CR Carve Up (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - CR - Joint Use Letter of Support (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - RR Interchanges (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - CR Labor - Management Project (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Bob Godwin's Aff. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gordon MacDougall (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - ATDD of BLE (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Exhibits to JFC's STB (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Surface Transportation Board Finance Docket (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Files and Finance Docket No. 33388 Volumes 1-4A. (Box 7)
  - Surface Transportation Board (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - CSX Corporation and CSX Transportation, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 4A of 8 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 2B of 8 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 2A of 8 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 1 of 8 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - JFC CR Merger (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Finance Docket No. 33388 Volumes 4B- 7B. (Box 8)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 4B of 8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 4C of 8 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 4E of 8 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 4F of 8 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 4G of 8 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 4D of 8 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 5 of 8 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 6A of 8 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 6B of 8 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 7A of 8 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume &B of 8 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 6C of 8 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Finance Docket No 33388 Volumes 7C- 8B and Applicants Rebuttal Volumes 1- 3B and Documents. (Box 9)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 8A of 8 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 3B of 3 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Applicants Rebuttal Volume 3A of 3 Public (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Applicants Rebuttal, Volume 2B of 3 Public-Redacted (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Applicants Rebuttal, Volume 2A of 3 Public-Redacted (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Applicants Rebuttal, Volume 1 of 3 Public-Redacted (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 8B of 8 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 7F of 8 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume7E of 8 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 7C of 8 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Finance Docket no. 33388, Volume 7D of 8 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Documents and Finance Docket No. 33388 Volume 8C. (Box 10)
  - Surface Transportation Board - Finance docket No. 33388 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CSX Environmental Report (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Surface Transportation Bd. - Finance Dockets (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Surface Transportation Bd. - Finance Dockets (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Finance Dockets No. 33388 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Surface Transportation Board - Finance Dockets No. 33388 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Surface Transportation Bd. - Finance Docket 33388 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Draft Environmental Impact Statements. (Box 11)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 5C (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Voume 3B (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 5A (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 3B (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 5B (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 3A (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 5A (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 6 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 4 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 6 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 4 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 5B (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Executive Summary (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Executive Summary (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Draft Environmental Impact Statement Volume 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, Memos, Reports, and Finance Docket No. 33388 Briefs. (Box 12)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Brief of Wisconsin Central Ltd. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Subject of Harassment /Intimidation of Injured Employees by Management Personnel (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - STB Finance Docket No. 33388 - Brief of Martin Marietta Materials, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Motion of Consumers Energy Company for Leave to File Supplemental Verified Statement on Newly-Revealed Contract Assignment Issues (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Northern Transportation Commission (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Illinois Railroad Company (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - STB Finance Docket No. 33388 - Indiana and Ohio Railway Company (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - STB Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - STB Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - STB Finance Docket no. 33388 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Correspondence and Finance Docket No. 33388 Briefs continued and Proposed Conrail Acquisitions Final Environmental Impact Statements. (Box 13)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 7 Addendum (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 6D (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 6C (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 6B (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 4 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 5 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 6A (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 3 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Executive Summary Volume (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "Proposed Conrail Acquisition" Final Environmental Impact Statement Volume 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Brief of Indiana Southern Railroad, Inc., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Brief of Ann Arbor Acquisition Corp. D/B/A Ann Arbor Railroad, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Brief of New England Central Railroad, Inc., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - APL Limited, Volume 2A - Public Appendix, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - APL Limited, Volume 1, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Applicants CSX Corp. and CSX Transportation, Inc., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Support of Comments and Request for Conditions by the PA House and Senate Transportation Committees, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Support of Comments by Northwest PA Rail Authority Seeking Reciprocal Overhead Trackage Rights, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Support of Request for Protective Conditions by Durham Transport, Inc., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - United States Department of Justice, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Rochester Gas and Electric Corporation, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Notice of Change in Position on behalf of Chicago Metra, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Withdrawal of Responsive Application by New York State Electric and Gas Corp. and Statement of Support for Primary Application, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Gateway Western Railway and the Gateway Eastern Railway, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Philadelphia Belt Line Railroad Company, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - City of Cleveland, Ohio, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - National Lime and Stone Company in Support of Protest and Request for Imposition of Conditions, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Centerior Energy Corporation, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Potomac Electric Power Company, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Transportation Communications International Union, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Illinois International Port District's Request for Conditions, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - National Mining Association, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - National Industrial Transportation League, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - Reading Blue Mountain & Northern Railroad Company, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388 - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Finance Docket No. 33388, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Invitation to Annual Meeting of Stockholders of Hollinger International, Inc., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Invitation to Annual Meeting of Shareholders of Boeing Company and Proxy Statement, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 41)